{
    "id": "282fbd3f92d74b9bb66f2e34e6c54dde",
    "title": "As, Like, As If",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She works .............................. a waitress.",
            "description": "As can be used to say what role a person or thing has.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59226a0f15bf4fdd9f0c7c10623e3a9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran ................................. wind.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4695a8cf6c044a75a4a559cc9862cbac"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... you know, we have to improve our productivity.",
            "description": "This is a common expression beginning with as.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like",
                "As if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a41146eb8ac647aa966214a22d0c033d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She walks ..................................... a duck.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "307a5ac5647743ca8b154ffb57a58432"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't cry .................................... a baby.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b7a03ed93ac47abb4255de3c63a31b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt ..................................... laughing.",
            "description": "I felt like laughing means I wanted to laugh.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad362efc9a614adaabfa9d2c6f63e5b9"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. a child, I used to be afraid of spiders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like",
                "As if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bac1771824b54bc883ba7e31d2eebd59"
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks .................................. a cat.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ba2887e48da84eaa9ba087b9807679a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks ................................... it is going to rain.",
            "description": "As if is used to say what a situation seems like. Like is possible here in a careless style. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bb98fc23cc8244469bc72fa2c64b87bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She talks .................................... she knew everything.",
            "description": "As if is used to say what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6fab18dd79be4a71aaf6c45ff04ac88c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat there smiling .................................... he had won a jackpot.",
            "description": "As if is used to say what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "422cf69c270b493f8d8d263a2f4fbc59"
        },
        {
            "question": "He fought ...................................... a lion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c6951886651c481f8f6f15833c38f8c5"
        }
    ]
}